

Yagboyaju Mukhtar Olasunkanmi

Product Designer

· Lagos, Nigeria

I am a product designer with eight months of experience. Within these months, I have worked with an early-staged startup and as a first time entrepreneur on conceptualizing and scaling ideas through viable design thinking & interaction process.

EXPERIENCE

CEO, **Hygeia.co** (Personal Project) February 2024 – till date

Hygeia.co is a health platform created for the sole purpose of providing in-depth health knowledge and care for individuals. It is basically a platform/ application that acts as a doctor, fitness coach and nutritionist.

- Created daily social marketing materials for the brands social platforms
- Designed users and brand side of the website UI interface
- Recreated the dashboard designs for users to publish tasks and personnels to fulfill tasks

Product Designer, Travrick

May 2024 - till date

Travrick is a social media application that combines features from Instagram, Netflix, and Twitter. It is considered an evolution of both streaming platforms and social media apps with combined features from both fields.

- Designed useful assets like sitemap, low and high fidelity prototype
- Worked closely with content writers and frontend developers to ensure a uniform art direction is expressed across
- Created a two break points scalable design that fits both mobile and desktop screens

Web devloper & Product Designer, Delta-cars

June 2024- September 2024

Delta-cars is a car-rental platform aimed at revolutionizing the car transportation system in Nigeria, a lot of Nigerians lack access to flexible car transportation which delta-cars aims to reverse. The idea is to provide flexible, efficient, ecnomic and reliable car rental services in order to provide Nigerians with maximum access to car transportation.

- Designed useful assets like sitemap, low and high fidelity prototype
- Worked closely with frontend developers to ensure a uniform art direction is expressed across
- Created a two break points scalable design that fits both mobile and desktop screens

Link: delta-car.vercel.app

(+234) 08125617036

mukhtaryagboyaju@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/mukhtaryagboyaju

CREATIVE SKILLS

User Interface Design
Interaction Design
Design system
Prototyping
User Research
Wireframing

TOOLS

Figma Figjam Adobe Illustrator Canva

SOFT SKILLS

Listening and speaking Problem solving Intrapersonal and empathy

EDUCATION

Google UX Design
Coursera UI Design
Coursera UX Research
Coursera Wireframing &
Prototyping
February 2024

University of Ilorin Undergraduate February 2024